(Sheldon:)You're welcome.
(Amy:)Do you realize
what's happening here?
(Howard:)Yeah, I do.
(Sheldon:)They're filling up on bread
and ruining their meal.
(Leonard:)Hey.
AMY: Hey.
(Amy:)What took you guys so long?
(Leonard:)Oh, we were following Howard,
but for some reason,
(Leonard:)he turned off his headlights
and went up a one-way street.
(Penny:)So, what did we miss?
(Alfred:)Oh, just Mary and I getting
to know each other a little.
(Mary:)Leonard, your father
is just charming.
(Beverly:)He's also broke.
(Beverly:)Did he mention that?
(Leonard:)Okay, Mom,
you sit over there...
And I'm gonna call Bernadette
and see what's keeping them.
(Sheldon:)If I'd known you were broke,
(Sheldon:)I wouldn't have made
a big deal about the bread.
(Bernadette(on phone):)Hey, Penny.
(Bernadette(on phone):)What are you talking about?
(Bernadette(on phone):)Oh, that was you?
(chuckles)